Here's how to spend 7 days in Iceland
away from the crowds. Start with the
classic Golden [music] Circle. It's a
great way to ease into Iceland. Make
sure to drop by a hot spring, an
essential Iceland experience. Get away
from the crowds [music] and head into
the highlands and drive on Iceland's
famous F-roads. Visit places such as
Kerlingarfjöll.
Continue to Landmannalaugar for
incredible scenery.
In Landmannalaugar, make sure to go on a
hike for breathtaking views of the
surrounding area.
Head south where you visit some of
Iceland's most famous sites along the
southern coast.
Visit Thakgil, a hidden valley
surrounded by steep green cliffs.
>> [music]
>> Visit Skaftafell National Park and swing
by Svartifoss before continuing to
Skaftafellsjökull glacier.
>> [music]
>> Go on a hike to visit this canyon with a
waterfall at the end.
And don't forget Jökulsárlón glacier
lagoon. And on the final day, visit
Vestrahorn before making the long drive
back towards Reykjavik.